{
    "id": "525f232594e24d7f8a7f569bd6504485",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I think ................................... time to call it quits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it's",
                "its"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ............................... do you speak English?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I like that teacher. She is ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks ..................................... French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got longer hair ................................ I have.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He attributed the failure of the project to .................................... lack of appeal to the masses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it's",
                "its"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. is a bridge across the river.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Their",
                "There"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They sent more food .................................. I had ordered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know anybody ................................... going to London in the next few weeks?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... coat is this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whose",
                "Who's"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}